ILGWU. Canadian Area films, 5780/038 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 2 membres, Aldea Guillemette, sounds (wild) office and clinic, union film, reel #2 (Box 4a, Folder 63)
- 1. Edlyn Whitehead, 2. Morris Feigelson (Box 4a, Folder 64)
  bob 3, 3 ¾ copie, union film, Anglais, dactylographie
- Riccianionetta 64, Anna 66, M. Lipari 65.1, Infantino 65.1, commencement [illegible] (Box 4a, Folder 65)
  Acetate
- Ambiance [illegible] (Box 4a, Folder 66)
- Cours: 3. Psychologie, 2-4 Langue Franc[ais], 1. Cinema; sync reunion depart [?] (Box 4a, Folder 67)
  sync 6 minutes fin; union film, 7 ½ NAB, original
- [no title] (Box 4a, Folder 68)
- CBC Discussion: Are big unions less democratic, Michael Chartrand, Bernard Shane, Prof. H.O. Woods (Box 4a, Folder 69)
- [no title] (Box 5)
  12" reel
- Les Midinetttes (Box 6)
  Italian; 16mm; film on cores; F150
- [Untitled] (Box 7)
  Includes 7 black and white snapshots of TV broadcast pickets in the can; "80' reversal film" written on can; F152
- "50,000", 1975 (Box 8)
  223'; 6:10min.; bilingual; F 153
- "ILGWU: La Mode Aujourd'hui" (Box 9)
  Omega Montreal Color Master, acetate, F154
- Fashion Today #5028 (Box 10)
  16mm; 27 min.; F155
- "Les Midinettes" (Box 11)
  English, Union Label Dept. Tempo Canada b/w, Bellevue Pathe (Quebec) Print copy 3, sound; F156
- [no title] (Box 12)
  Sent courtesy of Union Label Departmen; 13" reel, polyester, b/2; F157
- "Dany" (Box 13)
  French; color, 5" reel, polyester; F158
- "The Many Lengths of Fashion" (Box 14)
  F159
- "Marvin has it Made" (Box 15)
  color, 7" reel, polyester, F160
- "Mode 71 Fashion Films" (Box 16)
  English, print #7, color, 5" Polyester, F161
- "Who makes your clothes?" (Box 17)
  color, 7" reel, polyester, F162
- Union Syndicale "Greve" (Box 18)
  9" no reel, F163
- #5034, Spring and Summer Fashions, 1962 (Box 19)
  12" reel; F164